mango.com 2002-12-04

# Privacy and Information Security Policy

Mangosoft, Inc. ("Mangosoft") is committed to safeguarding your online privacy with respect to the personally identifiable information that Mangosoft may obtain from you at the [www.mangosoft.com](http://www.mangosoft.com/) web site (the "Web Site"). Our Privacy Policy answers frequently asked questions about your online privacy, including what personally identifiable information we may obtain from you and how it will be used and protected. Mangosoft may from time to time change this Privacy Policy, so please check back periodically. 

* * *

## Privacy and the MangomindSM Service

### HOW DO WE PROTECT THE SECURITY AND QUALITY OF THE INFORMATION AND FILES STORED ON THE MANGOMIND SERVICE?

Mangomind has been designed to offer the best-in-class security architecture by strong encryption applied exclusively at the client in combination with world-class challenge/response authentication. 

**Data you place on the Mangomind service is encrypted before it leaves your computer. This data remains encrypted on the servers and is not accessible in any decrypted form to Mangosoft or anyone with access to the Mangomind servers. Then, only after it is downloaded by you or those you specifically invite to access your Mangomind drives is it ever decrypted.**

**We believe that Mangomind is so secure that information and files you place on the Mangomind service just as secure, if not more secure, than the data stored on servers in your private LANs.**

Mangomind's connection authentication and data encryption components are described briefly here. For a more thorough description, please see the Mangomind Security White Paper. 

  * **Connection Authentication**. When a Mangomind client computer connects to the Mangomind server, Connection Authentication validates that both are who they say they are. This means that someone else cannot pretend to be a Mangomind server, tricking your Mangomind software into sending it your data. And vice-versa -- no Mangomind client that you haven't invited to the drive can trick a Mangomind server into sending it your data. This authentication is performed through a challenge/response protocol using the RSA Public/Private key pairs of both parties. Every new connection made must successfully complete the challenge protocol.
  * **Data Encryption**. Mangomind encrypts your data using RSA 128 bit RC5 data encryption keys. Your data is encrypted with these keys on your Mangomind client just before it is sent on the wire to the Mangomind server. Once on the server, it remains encrypted. At no point after leaving your computer can anyone view the clear text version of your files. Most importantly, we employ a unique encryption key management system so that the usable keys are only available on the client machines. Only the client computer can download and then decrypt the data. Since the usable keys are not available anywhere on the server, no one can view your data by looking at the data contained there. Even the names of your files are changed on the server to meaningless strings so as not to hint at their contents.

* * *

## Privacy and the Mangosoft Web Sites

### WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DO WE OBTAIN FROM YOU? WHEN DO WE OBTAIN SUCH INFORMATION?

If, upon visiting our Web Site, your use is limited to browsing our informational content, we will not require that you provide us with any personally identifiable information. 

However, we may request personal information from you at other times. For example: 

  * If you purchase products on our Web Site, we will ask that you provide us with certain personal information, including your name, credit card number, expiration date, password, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone
  * If you use the Mangomind service, we will ask that you provide us with your name, password, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number.
  * If you want to enter any contests or promotions sponsored by us [or by one of our business partners], we will need your name, e-mail address and other information as may be required by the rules of the specific contest.
  * If you choose to participate in a customer survey conducted by us or by one of our business partners, we may ask for your name, e-mail address and other information as may be required by the particular survey.
  * If you report a problem or submit a customer review, we will ask that you provide your name and e-mail address, although you can choose not to have your name and/or e-mail address submitted to us. Should you contact us for any reason other than to report a problem and/or submit a review, we may also keep a record and/or copy of your correspondence with us.

### HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

Our primary use of your information is to administer, maintain and improve your experience on our Web Site generally as well as provide you with customized, personalization services and interactive communications. 

  * We may from time to time send you e-mails regarding our Web Site and special promotions. Also, we occasionally may send you direct mail about products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
  * We use your financial information (e.g., your credit card number) only to verify your credit and to bill you for products purchased on our Web Site. We also use your contact information as necessary to send you the products that you have purchased on our Web Site.
  * When you enter any contests or promotions sponsored by us or by one of our business partners, we may use your e-mail address to send you status updates.
  * We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the services offered on our Web Site. We also use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that we may share with our business partners, but only in the aggregate without any of your personally identifiable information.
  * We may research the demographics, interests and behavior of our customers based on the information provided to us upon registration, during promotions and contests, from our server log files, from cookies and from surveys. Our research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this aggregate data with business partners, but only in the aggregate, without any of your personally identifiable information.

### PRIVACY POLICIES OF MANGOSOFT'S PARTNERS

Third parties that have links on our Web Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such sites and the practices of these sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. If you have questions about the privacy policies or practices of a third party site, you should contact the site administrator or web-master of the specific site. 

We may from time to time partner with other companies to offer co-branded services as well as sweepstakes, contests and promotions. Any information that you provide in connection with the co-branded services or any jointly sponsored sweepstakes, contests or promotions will become the joint property of Mangosoft and its business partners. We will maintain your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. However, this Privacy Policy does not govern the privacy policies and practices of our business partners. If you have questions about the privacy policies or practices of our business partners, you should contact them directly. 

### DO WE SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

No, as a general rule, we do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any one. If and whenever we intend to share your personally identifiable information with a third party (other than to a business partner as provided herein), you will be notified at the time of data collection or transfer, and you will have the option of not permitting the transfer. However, we may from time to time rent or sell demographic information in the aggregate that does not contain your personally identifiable information. 

### WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE INFORMATION?

We generally will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission to do so or under some special circumstances described below. 

  * As noted previously, we may from time to time partner with other companies to offer co-branded services as well as sweepstakes, contests and promotions. Any information that you provide in connection with the co-branded services or any jointly sponsored sweepstakes, contests or promotions will become the joint property of Mangosoft and its business partners. We may also disclose other personal information about you to our business partners, but only if we have obtained your permission to make the disclosure before data collection or before transferring the data.
  * We may, from time to time, offer you the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you want to receive this information, we may (but only with your permission) share your name and e-mail address with them.
  * Under confidentiality agreements, we may match user information with third party data. We also may disclose aggregate demographic and/or user information and statistics in order to describe our customer base to prospective partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.
  * We may disclose your personally identifiable information without your prior permission in special cases. For example, we may have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the User Terms and Conditions, or may be causing intentional or unintentional injury or interference to the rights or property of Mangosoft or any third party, including other customers. Also, we may disclose or access your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that law or regulation requires disclosure.

### WHAT ARE COOKIES? HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?

Cookies enable us to customize and personalize your experience on our Web Site, including the products and promotions that are offered to you. Essentially, a cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and is stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for several purposes in connection with the operation of our Web Site. 

  * Most important, we use cookies to identify you and access your information stored on our computers in order to deliver you a better and more personalized experience. For example, we use cookies to tell you about products and services specific to your interests.
  * We use cookies to save your password so that you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our Web Site.
  * We use cookies to estimate our customer base and customer usage patterns. Each browser accessing our Web Site is given a unique cookie that is then used to determine the extent of repeat visits and the customer activity during those visits. We use the historical information to help target promotions based on customer interests and behavior, both specifically to individual customers and on an aggregate basis with respect to all customers.
  * We also may use cookies to track your progress and number of entries in some promotions, sweepstakes and contests. For example, when a promotion uses cookies, the information coded to the cookie indicates your progress through the promotion, and may be used to track entries, submissions and status of prize drawings.

Business partners that offer co-branded services and jointly-sponsored sweepstakes, contests and promotions on our Web Site, may use their own cookies. We have no control over those cookies, nor does this Privacy Policy cover how your personal information contained in those cookies may be used or protected. If you have any questions about the cookies of such third parties, or about the use of your personal information by such third parties, you should contact the site administrator or web-master of the third party site. 

### DO YOU HAVE CHOICES ABOUT COOKIES?

Yes, you have several choices with respect to cookies. You can modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. However, if you choose to reject all cookies, you may not be able to participate in promotions, or purchase any products or services, offered by us if registration is a requirement of participation or purchase. 

### HOW CAN YOU UPDATE, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

You may edit your personally identifiable information and your password at any time by sending an e-mail to [webmaster@mangosoft.com](mailto:webmaster@mangosoft.com) and describing the changes to be made. 

### HOW DO WE PROTECT THE SECURITY AND QUALITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION POSTED TO OUR WEB SITES?

We have also taken steps to help protect the integrity of your personal financial information when you complete a purchase transaction on our Web Site. Specifically, we use VeriSign and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to facilitate confidential online business transactions. VeriSign and SSL help prevent your credit card number, name, address and telephone number from being read by unauthorized persons as this information is transmitted over the Internet. Also, we transfer your personal information to our secure server as soon as we receive your order. 

### WHAT ELSE SHOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT YOUR ONLINE PRIVACY?

It is important to remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on-line, your information can be collected and used by others. If you transmit or post personal information on-line that is accessible to others, you will not be able to control how that information is used by others. When we receive the transmitted information, we will use the procedures summarized in this Privacy Policy to ensure the integrity and security of that information in our systems. Unfortunately, notwithstanding any of the steps taken by us, it is not possible to guarantee the security and integrity of data transmitted over the Internet. Consequently, while we take the above-described reasonable steps to protect your personal information, we cannot and do not warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us when registering for our Web Site or otherwise. All such transmission of information is at your own risk. Moreover, though we are committed to having our Web Site comply with this Privacy Policy, you are ultimately responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and your personally identifiable information. If you are careless with your password, or you decide to share your password with third parties, you must be aware of the risk that such third parties will have access to all your personally identifiable information. 

### CONTACTING US

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement or the practices of our Web Site, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@mangosoft.com](mailto:webmaster@mangosoft.com)
